[ Watch on kissFlix.co ]
I asked the guys at the motor pool.
They checked it over.
Said the engine isn't leaking oil,
and the wiring is fine too.
The oil and filter were both changed.
They haven't found any specific issues for now.
Avoid shifting gears too frequently,
and don't press the clutch too hard.
Avoid sudden acceleration or braking.
At the intersection we just passed,
there's a specialized hospital to the southwest.
Is it dermatology or maternity?
It was too far to see clearly.
Is there a problem with that hospital?
If necessary,
I can go back and check right now.
If you can't remember a hospital,
you can go back and look again.
But if you can't remember a conversation?
Will you ask them to repeat it?
From now on, the people I meet,
the words they say,
everything I need to remember,
I will remember it all.
You definitely won't remember.
Who do you think you are?
Three lines from one person is hard enough.
What about ten people?
Sometimes at a dinner,
there are over a dozen strangers.
What they say is half-true, half-false.
Which line has a double meaning,
which sentence has a hidden meaning...
You won't even understand it when you hear it.
How will you remember?
I heard some have naturally good memory.
I really don't have that talent.
But I want to try.
I don't know how to remember everything,
but there must be a trick to it, right?
Force yourself.
The brain is like a stomach.
If you can't eat, force it down.
Sooner or later, you'll stretch it out.
Lao Wei asked me to grade you all.
For me, it's very simple.
Just this one thing.
If you can remember, you stay.
If you can't, I'm sending you back.
What are you thinking about?
Cursing me in your head?
I'm memorizing what you just said.
From now on,
every person you meet,
every word they say,
every office you enter,
every restaurant,
every shop.
Whether the people you meet
are on the street or at home,
in a teahouse or a dance hall,
no matter how noisy the setting is,
you will remember everything.
Every day before getting off work,
whether it's at seven,
or at twelve,
you will recite to me what they said.
You can't forget it even after reciting.
Don't even think about fooling me.
If I catch you once,
you're out.
My uncle...
he really does live in here.
He lives right inside, Building 3, Unit 2,
Room 101.
Room 101, right?
Then sign in here.
Brother Qi.
Done.
I can't believe you bluffed your way in.
What did you tell them this time?
I said my aunt and uncle both live here,
and I came to see them.
Lies just roll off your tongue.
Didn't they ask for their names,
or which room they're in?
They did.
What did you say?
I told the truth.
Because my aunt and uncle really live here.
Ever since you were little,
you've always been this...
serious.
What are you doing here?
My uncle lives around here.
Just came to visit.
What about you?
Uncle?
I thought Old Wu was your brother-in-law?
Does he live around here too?
No.
I figured it's all family anyway.
And you?
I'm here to find someone.
Your brother-in-law.
He insisted on showing me some textile mill.
It's about to go out of business.
Acting like they have strict rules.
They blocked the gate with a steel plate.
I had to take a crap.
Almost shit my pants.
Do you know what I used to wipe?
I've done that too.
I've even used stones and leaves.
None of those beat a wall corner!
Right.
Where's my brother-in-law?
Where is he?
Let's go.
"Amazing Tales" says the truth can't be faked.
If you tell a lie,
you have to find someone to cover it up.
As long as he's real, you won't be exposed.
Where's my brother-in-law?
Where is he?
He was just here.
Give me a ride! Give me a ride!
Okay.
Where to?
Boss Lin.
Old Wu.
You're not up yet?
Can we see that textile mill you mentioned?
I happen to be free right now.
Are you free?
Okay, okay, okay.
I'm hanging up.
The cops are here! The cops are here!
Where did he go?
We'll get back to work then.
Hurry up, I'm in a rush.
Hurry, hurry, hurry!
Where did they go?
Come with me to the post office.
Hurry up and fix your car.
Make sure you don't block the road.
What's their problem?
Stop the car!
Watch out!
If we rush the arrest,
Aren't we going straight in?
it would alert the target.
Are you going to tip him off?
Find the number for the security section.
Hand it to me when it connects.
Hello.
Please transfer me to the security section.
Who's calling?
Hello, Minzhong State Security Bureau.
We'd like to ask Fan Chen a few questions.
Speaking.
What's this about?
Sorry.
The person we're looking for is a woman.
She probably has the same name as you.
Who is it?
Who called?
The sorting room.
Gotta finish sorting the parcels.
Telling me to get back to work.
We just ran out of water.
The bosses want tea,
so I'm running errands.
Must be tough.
That's life.
Here you go.
Hi, where's the Security Section?
Can I help you?
Police business.
It's right here.
Lao Fan.
Lao Fan!
Who are you looking for?
I'm Lao Fan's friend.
He told me to meet him in this room.
Where is he?
He just went to get hot water.
Where's the hot water room?
Go through the sorting room,
and it's downstairs.
What are you doing?
Are you crazy?!
Watch where you're going!
Cuff him.
Get up.
What were you thinking?
Showing your hand right from the start.
Who taught you that?
Sorry, Brother Qi.
I didn't expect him to be in the security section.
I'll definitely remember this.
And take it as a lesson.
Remember my ass.
Do you even need to memorize that?
Your brain just doesn't know how to pivot.
I'll try to pivot more from now on.
What the hell is wrong with you!
No, no.
The car in front slammed on the brakes.
Brother Qi.
Maybe we should just let it go.
We still have to interrogate that postman.
Brother Qi!
Look.
Brother Qi, just let it go.
This has nothing to do with you.
Please wait here for a second.
Just a moment.
Kill the engine.
Stop the car!
Hello.
Please show your ID and driver's license.
And vehicle registration.
I was in a rush today and forgot them.
Let's go, move.
Take this seriously.
Driver, you're looking at
driving without a license,
reckless driving,
and no vehicle registration.
Frankly, you're in big trouble.
Hold on.
Where's the accomplice in the passenger seat?
Officer,
I really have urgent business.
You have to let me go.
Otherwise, you'll be in big trouble.
Let's go.
Fine, let's go.
Move, move, move.
I was just busy.
An oxcart rear-ended a bicycle.
Awaiting orders, Captain.
Right, right.
Which department?
Is that so?
Well, they didn't mention that.
Understood. We'll definitely cooperate.
Let them through immediately.
What do these numbers mean?
I don't know.
I'm just a courier.
I only deliver messages.
Such a small piece of paper.
You didn't keep it at home,
but insisted on hiding it here.
Doesn't your tooth hurt?
I know this is very important,
but who it's for,
I have no idea.
You can check if you don't believe me.
These are the rules.
If you were my superior,
would you let me know?
What is it?
You're not going up, right?
All right.
He's finally back.
Where's the car?
I drove it back.
It's parked in the yard.
How did you get through?
Tell us all about it,
so we can learn a thing or two.
According to the Traffic Penalty Regulations,
directing traffic for 80 minutes is enough.
The traffic police said so.
There's no such rule in the regulations.
I'm positive.
If he says there is, there is.
It's the same for rule breakers.
But when the time was up, he wasn't there.
So I just drove the car back myself.
How about that postman?
Did he confess?
Comrades, let's pack up.
Once Old Wei comes back,
we'll search Fan Chen's home and office.
He confessed.
Why don't you go ask him?
His hometown is Shishi.
He went to Taiwan, China when he was young.
He's a good photographer.
He accidentally killed someone.
They got him out of prison
and into the "Military Intelligence Bureau".
He initially worked at a state photo studio.
Later he was transferred to the post office,
where he's worked until now.
Who are these codes for?
Do we have a rough idea?
He's right.
If I were his boss, I wouldn't tell him either.
But this guy is smart.
From the clues,
he has a guess.
Yesterday at 3:10 PM,
he put this code and a gold bar
next to Taijiang Department Store,
in an abandoned mailbox.
According to the original plan,
someone was to pick it up within ten minutes.
Next to Taijiang Department Store
is Institute 761.
Regarding the missiles...
We have a thief on our hands.
But the other party didn't pick it up.
This mailbox has been scrapped since then,
and won't be used again.
If they don't take it today,
what about tomorrow?
Or the day after?
Institute 761 holds the key to the missiles.
The enemy is practically drooling over it.
Out of thousands of people at Institute 761,
a wavering traitor is hiding among them.
Who could it be?
What cards are the Communists going to play?
How will they play them?
You have to show me the cards, Old Zheng.
With intelligence,
you can't just wait.
You have to go out and grab it.
What about the missile progress?
Answer me!
I didn't eat much for lunch.
I can't hold on much longer.
I'll go buy some water for everyone.
Please get me eight bottles of soda,
boss.
Take care, sir.
We look forward to your next visit.
The missile intel-
You scared me to death!
I thought it was the Communists.
There might be an issue with the missile intel.
My mole in the mainland's State Security
sent a message saying
Professor Cao's courier was caught.
He hasn't met the professor,
and doesn't know any information.
Even if he breaks and talks,
the mainland won't learn our secrets.
Plus, the latest handover wasn't completed.
This actually works in our favor.
Are you delivering good news or bad news?
Or a mix of both?
It happened suddenly.
If by any chance
we don't get the Institute 761 intel on time...
You mean to say,
you want me to come up with a plan for you?
I heard
you're meeting the higher-ups tomorrow.
I rushed here to brief you,
so you wouldn't be
put on the defensive.
I'm already on the defensive.
Confucius said, "If a man lacks trust,
I know not what he can accomplish."
Last time you said
there'd be no problem.
With tomorrow's meeting,
I don't even dare to go.
You go to the meeting in my place.
If there's no main dish,
just pile the side dishes high.
Do we have the map of the naval pier?
Is the military exercise intel accurate?
Don't you have a lot of informants?
If we have nothing at all,
we might as well pack it in early
and go home to farm.
Let's go.
Brother Qi.
Hello, Minzhong State Security Bureau.
We'd like to ask Fan Chen a few questions.
Where did you go?
Come with me to the post office.
Have you read this book?
I've heard of it.
Haven't read it yet.
Do you like reading?
I like Jin Yong.
You said you've seen this man.
When?
Where?
Before I attended the training class.
He delivered a parcel to me.
You were home?
No. 02, Lane 75.
He came three times.
No one was home.
So I came to catch you right when I got to work.
What a coincidence.
That's my newly rented place.
According to him,
the letters and telegrams in that area
are all delivered by him.
Right, Brother Qi.
How did you know
he'd come out the back door of those houses?
Why didn't you chase him when he ran?
It happened so fast.
I didn't expect him to come out.
I didn't react in time.
If I were the boss,
I'd suspect you.
What are you trying to say?
Suspecting me for no reason.
Suspecting our own people.
Is that a division rule or a bureau rule?
So you need to turn yourself into a map.
As small as this street,
or as big as the city, countryside, and province.
Every alley, every intersection,
every well, every tree,
must be etched into your mind.
Even if you're blindfolded,
you should be able to cross the city.
If I were him,
I would've come out from there too.
I would've taken a gamble too.
Gambled on whether the one guarding there
was a rookie,
an idiot,
or an ally.
Never suspecting anyone in your life,
and never being suspected,
means you've lived in vain.
What does it mean to be an investigator?
In my eyes,
Old Wei could also be
a mole for the "Military Intelligence Bureau".
I don't know what's inside.
This is a box someone sent him.
Is there a problem?
The wooden boards are too thick.
Light can't shine through.
You can't see anything.
General on Horseback.
I haven't seen this type of lock before.
It won't be easy to open.
Give me a hammer.
Here, let me take a picture first.
Okay.
I won't be able to put it back together.
Won't open it just because you can't fix it?
If you fear choking, just stop eating.
Let the Tech Section look at it.
Do not open it before entering the darkroom.
Brother Qi.
Come take a look over here.
How much force did it take
to jump down from above
and leave such a deep footprint?
He definitely escaped out the back window.
Before I entered the room during the day,
someone else had also been here.
Tenth floor.
Early out, late in, acting all mysterious.
You,
what kind of business are you in exactly?
Just running a small business.
Socializing is inevitable.
Young man,
you need to take good care of your health.
Thanks.
Sponge cakes, fried dough sticks, tea eggs
Two mao
Everyone says you're leaving.
Xiao Lei from Division 3 was asking me today.
He said your paperwork is at the final step.
What are your thoughts?
I can still work for here from the outside.
It's all the same.
Are you really planning to leave?
That's classified.
That guy you caught yesterday...
He doesn't seem to be very high-ranking.
Our Division 2...
We even mobilized thermoses and mops.
All that fuss for nothing.
It wasn't exactly for nothing.
It just feels, how should I put it...
Like shooting a mosquito with a cannon.
Exactly.
Shooting a mosquito with a cannon.
Alright, alright.
At least you guys get to run around.
We have to review files every day.
Surviving purely on coffee.
Reviewing from morning until dawn.
My eyes are going blind from all the reading.
That coffee of yours...
You're better off drinking nutritious milk.
I thought we'd get to carry guns.
But when I asked right before leaving...
We didn't even get batons.
I was even hoping for bulletproof vests.
Long pants and sleeves are still necessary.
If you happen to scrape the ground,
you could easily skin your arms and legs.
It was just a small fry.
You and Brother Qi could've handled him.
Why use a sledgehammer to crack a nut?
It really wasn't satisfying.
Before I even realized what was happening,
the guy was already caught.
When will we get to work on a big case?
You'll just have to wait for a big case.
Director Wu.
Just a reminder.
Those of us in intelligence work
should habitually lower our voices
by an octave,
anywhere we go.
Unless...
you want to give a speech.
Have a seat.
Like using a marble slab to press a pickle jar.
You all must feel underutilized.
What counts as a big case?
How many people must be arrested?
How many buildings blown up?
How many cars crashed?
How much of the state's money must be spent
for it to count as a big case?
You...
Minor intel is beneath you, isn't it?
I'll tell you what.
In one week's time,
gather all the world's
nuclear submarine blueprints
and put them on my desk.
Earth-shattering, isn't it?
Doing intelligence work,
you have to shock Taiwan, China first,
then scare the Americans
into wetting their pants and shoes.
Pretty impressive, right?
A real moment of glory!
Catching spies.
You want to be issued guns.
Submachine guns, even.
And catch dozens of spies at once.
Have you ever considered,
if there really were such an operation,
how many enemies would die?
How many of our comrades
might have to sacrifice their lives?
If there really were such a big case,
behind it,
how many state secrets would have been leaked?
How many people would face the firing squad?
How many children
would wake up in the morning
to find their parents gone?
And how many white-haired elders,
in a single day,
would lose
the sons meant to care for them in their old age?
Answer me.
On the hidden front...
think it through before you speak.
Go to my office after you eat.
Once you've thought it through,
come and tell me.
Fickle.
Shifting loyalties.
Still restless after your transfer.
Wanting to leave when you're in the bureau,
and wanting to come back once you're out.
Nobody knows what you really want to do.
In intelligence work,
you must blend truth and fiction.
Everyone in the bureau now knows
your affiliation is with Section 1.
But in reality, your true superior
is Section Chief Wei.
Whether it's a secondment,
or just rumors,
they're all smokescreens.
From now on,
no matter the lie, you can cover it up,
and make it plausible.
Chief Wei thinks I'm suited to be a tour guide.
Am I really guiding a tour to Wuyi Mountain?
Being a tour guide is great.
You can go anywhere.
If I were 30 years younger,
I'd jump at the chance to do this job.
You can visit Wuyi Mountain,
and Gulangyu too.
I have zero experience in intelligence work.
Why was I chosen?
Section Chief Wei's report stated that,
among your batch of new recruits,
relatively speaking,
you are outstanding,
and quite unique.
You also have a gender advantage.
Most importantly,
intelligence work
requires talent.
What is your name?
Yu Lixia.
Letting it go to your head?
Always remember,
your name is Jin Lan.
You must completely forget the name Yu Lixia.
Starting today,
you must do your best to cut off
contact with your friends and classmates.
Every task in the bureau,
every single matter,
must be kept secret from everyone.
Do you know why?
Because of organizational discipline.
Because intelligence work
involves turned assets.
If there's a leak,
they could lose their heads.
A single sentence from you,
or even a single word,
could mean a living, breathing life.
Perhaps one day,
a suitable friend,
someone you need to befriend,
will fall right into your lap.
When that day comes,
that will be the time you resign,
or transfer out.
A friend?
How do I make this friend?
When will they come?
You wait.
In intelligence work,
the most important thing is waiting patiently.
Anything else to add?
I didn't have lunch.
I'm running on empty.
You said you've seen this man.
When?
Where?
Before the training course.
He delivered a package to me.
Why didn't you go after him when he ran?
I was caught off guard.
I didn't expect him to come out.
If I were your superior,
I would suspect you.
I think He Chunxiao is suspicious.
Whatever you do,
whatever you do,
do not baselessly suspect
your own comrades and brothers in arms.
Unless
you have ironclad evidence.
You missed something.
Missed what?
You left out four details.
Which parts did I miss?
Figure it out yourself.
Was it at the textile mill?
Where we met my brother-in-law?
Are you asking me?
We said so much today,
and went to so many places.
Can you really remember it all?
Would I be testing you if I couldn't?
From the first second you opened your eyes,
think carefully.
One mistake, you buy me dinner.
Two mistakes,
you run laps around the track.
Three mistakes,
you're out.
What are you doing here?
My uncle lives around here.
I came to visit.
What about you?
I'm looking for someone.
It's your brother-in-law.
He insisted on showing me some textile mill.
It's about to go under.
Who's this?
It's me, brother-in-law.
My sister says you're at the office every day.
Why aren't you home yet?
I'm working overtime.
What's up? Do you need something?
The thing is...
Is that textile factory about to go under?
I saw you visiting the factory the other day.
Are they planning a buyout?
How would I know?
What are you getting at?
He might not invest,
but you still showed him around.
Isn't that just how you guys do business?
You cast your net whether there's fish or not, right?
Here's the thing, brother-in-law.
My uncle's kid...
You met him at my place for New Year's.
The one who's taller than me.
He's been sitting around at home lately.
If that Lin Kanshan
really acquires the textile factory,
I was thinking,
could you get him a job there?
Wait for the deal to close before giving out jobs.
Anything else?
I've been showing the investors from Taiwan, China around.
These guys are real workaholics.
Looking around everywhere every day.
If that's all, I'm going to hang up.
I'm really busy right now.
Alright, brother-in-law.
Okay.
Investigate the latest naval port deployments
and details of recent exercises.
Report back immediately.
What are you doing?
Do you know where you are?
You're filming a naval pier.
Defense facilities are highly classified.
Leaking info can get you arrested and jailed.
Hand it over.
Don't move.
Beat it.
Section Chief Wei.
I'd like to request a new partner.
What's wrong with Hua Dong?
He Chunxiao complements me better.
Changing partners is like dating.
How do I know who fits better without spending time?
It's not a blind date. You don't have to commit.
What's the harm in switching?
You said it.
So, do you mean this is temporary...
...or permanent?
We have an operation today anyway.
If it's a good fit, it'll be permanent.
If not, it's temporary.
All right.
You're here.
What'll it be?
The usual.
Got it, the usual.
Here, your flatbread.
And your porridge.
Here you go.
Take care.
Thanks.
You're welcome.
Tailing is our magnifying glass.
Observe the target's walking habits.
Does he usually step with his left foot...
...or his right foot?
See if, while walking, he...
...subconsciously touches his pockets.
You also need to read the environment.
Which shop's window...
...can reflect the target's movements.
Which intersection...
...allows us to take cover quickly.
Looking so eagerly,
are you looking for me or a girlfriend?
Have you ever been in love?
What?
Never chased a girl?
It's the kind where in the whole world,
you only have eyes for her.
You can't see anyone else but her.
Even if a thief
reached into your pocket, you wouldn't notice.
Just like right now.
Tailing someone is the same.
Total single-mind...
How do you say that word again?
Edness.
I'll make your brain think about
how to spell "single-mindedness".
Once you're distracted, I can strike.
Your anti-tracking awareness is zero.
Why are you secretly following me?
Apply what you learn. You said it.
I wanted to try it out too.
In future surveillance operations,
how can I avoid being spotted?
That depends on who you are monitoring.
Tailing a second grader,
you probably won't be exposed.
A third grader is hard to say.
Tell me.
Who is the target on your mind?
A businessman from Taiwan, China.
In the nightclub restroom,
the one who helped me out.
Is there a problem?
I saw him in the post office backyard.
Theoretically speaking,
his movement trajectory is suspicious.
But I verified it.
He does have a legitimate reason.
So I can't really say.
Think it through before you speak then.
Focus on getting today's job done first.
What's the job today?
A huge op only young people can handle.
Didn't anyone notify you?
From the city center to Mawei,
around the docks and near the schools,
check the utility poles one by one.
Look carefully at every single one.
There are ads for photography enthusiasts,
specifically to take pictures of the docks.
Mailing addresses,
pager numbers,
and identity info must all be memorized.
Track and investigate them one by one.
The Taiwan Strait situation is escalating.
The "Military Intelligence Bureau" is overreaching.
Intel on the naval dock is a priority.
We must catch the elephants,
and the mosquitoes too.
Today, we are here to catch mosquitoes.
Two people per group.
Divide and zone the areas.
Upset that I swapped you out?
Don't want to go out?
Sitting in the office drinking tea is nice.
No.
Brother Qi made me recount everything that happens,
every word spoken,
every person met,
and everything done, all clearly.
He checks it every day.
One more mistake and he'll drop me.
He only knows how to make demands of others.
Can he remember all that himself?
He really can.
I asked.
I don't know if he has a trick,
or if some just have a naturally good memory.
I am Wang Kai.
Inviting you to watch the TV drama
Crossfire.
Dried shrimp prices in the market were stable,
but suddenly went up.
The county hospital
and Chengguan Town Hospital's heatstroke meds
are selling much more than usual.
This unit most likely
is from the Beijing Military Region, unaccustomed to humidity.
The people over there
want to catch a big fish.
How big?
As big as a missile.
The 761 Institute recently made a breakthrough
in missile fuel.
They are definitely coming for this.
Something big is going to happen.
Are you crazy!
Why are you so nervous?